But, you know, this is a relationship podcast, and I will say, I say this everywhere I can because it was a game changer for me.
And my therapist, when I was asking her about Devon, she was like, the difference between Devon and the last person you were seeing is that he makes decisions to make his life better.
Your ex made decisions to make himself feel better.
Because it may not always feel good to do the things that you need to do to make your life better.
That's right.
It does not feel good.
I think a lot of people don't understand, like, this whole, like, partners thing and long-term partnership thing, people really only think about dating.
And they really don't talk about just, like, the journey of, like, a long-term partnership is ups and downs that, for the most part, aren't even about you and the person.
Like, it's ups and downs of health, ups and downs of their family, ups and downs of career, ups and downs of mental health.
Like, the ups and downs of just the ebb and flow of life.
People don't write songs about that.
People don't write songs about, like, my man lost his job, but I'm riding for him.
Like, you know, like, they don't write that song.
And you're, like, I mean, when I was a singer, I wrote that song.
I wrote a song called This Who Shall Pass.
Like, because, like, I feel like that's the stuff that people don't really talk about in terms of how this whole relationship thing really ends up being a dance of how to ride the waves together.
This Who Shall Pass